ศาล	NN	O	B_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
ให้	CC	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
"	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เอ็นบีที	NN	B_ORG	E_CLS

ฝาก	VV	O	B_CLS
ขัง	VV	O	I_CLS
แล้ว	AX	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
"	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นักรบศรีวิชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
"	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พนง.สส.	NN	B_DES	I_CLS
สน.	NN	B_LOC	I_CLS
สุทธิสาร	NN	E_LOC	I_CLS
แจ้ง	VV	O	I_CLS
ความ	FX	O	I_CLS
ผิด	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ข้อหา	NN	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ร่วม	VV	O	I_CLS
กัน	PR	O	I_CLS
บุกรุก	VV	O	I_CLS
สำนักงาน	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
สถานี	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
โทรทัศน์	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
เอ็นบีที	NN	E_ORG	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
มี	VV	O	I_CLS
อาวุธ	NN	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
และ	CC	O	B_CLS
ใช้	VV	O	I_CLS
กำลัง	NN	O	I_CLS
ประทุษร้าย	VV	O	E_CLS

พร้อม	CC	O	B_CLS
ร้อง	VV	O	I_CLS
ศาล	NN	O	I_CLS
ค้าน	VV	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	I_CLS
กลัว	VV	O	I_CLS
หลบหนี	VV	O	E_CLS

ขณะ	CC	O	B_CLS
ที่	CC	O	I_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ราย	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ขอ	VV	O	I_CLS
ยื่น	VV	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	E_CLS
แต่	CC	O	B_CLS
ศาล	NN	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
อนุญาต	VV	O	E_CLS

ตาม	PS	O	B_CLS
คำ	NN	O	I_CLS
ร้อง	VV	O	I_CLS
ระบุ	VV	O	I_CLS
ว่า	CC	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
คดี	NN	O	I_CLS
เจ้าหน้าที่	NN	O	I_CLS
ตำรวจ	NN	O	I_CLS
สามารถ	AX	O	I_CLS
จับกุม	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
พร้อม	VV	O	I_CLS
ของกลาง	NN	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
อาทิ	CC	O	B_CLS
_	PU	O	O
อาวุธ	NN	O	B_CLS
ปืน	NN	O	I_CLS
พก	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
3	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
กระบอก	CL	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พร้อม	VV	O	I_CLS
เครื่อง	NN	O	I_CLS
กระสุน	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มีด	NN	O	I_CLS
ดาบ	NN	O	E_CLS
และ	CC	O	B_CLS
มีด	NN	O	I_CLS
ปลาย	NN	O	I_CLS
แหลม	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
วิทยุ	NN	O	I_CLS
สื่อสาร	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
หนังสติ๊ก	NN	O	I_CLS
พร้อม	VV	O	I_CLS
กระสุน	NN	O	I_CLS
ลูก	NN	O	I_CLS
หิน	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
ของกลาง	NN	O	I_CLS
อื่น	AJ	O	I_CLS
ๆ	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
25	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รายการ	CL	O	E_CLS

ต่อมา	CC	O	B_CLS
ทนายความ	NN	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
สภา	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
ทนายความ	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
ยื่น	VV	O	I_CLS
คำ	NN	O	I_CLS
ร้อง	VV	O	I_CLS
พร้อม	VV	O	I_CLS
หลักทรัพย์	NN	O	I_CLS
เป็น	VV	O	I_CLS
เงินสด	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	O	I_CLS
ละ	AJ	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
แสน	NN	O	I_CLS
บาท	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
ขอ	VV	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นาย	NN	B_TTL	I_CLS
นิติรัตน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทรัพย์สมบูรณ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
แกนนำ	NN	O	I_CLS
สมัชชา	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
คน	NN	O	I_CLS
จน	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
กับ	PS	O	I_CLS
นาย	NN	B_TTL	I_CLS
นัสเซอร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ยีหมะ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
13	NU	B_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
14	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อย่างไรก็ตาม	CC	O	I_CLS
ขณะนี้	NN	O	I_CLS
อยู่	VV	O	I_CLS
ระหว่าง	PS	O	I_CLS
รอ	VV	O	I_CLS
ศาล	NN	O	I_CLS
พิจารณา	VV	O	I_CLS
ไต่สวน	VV	O	I_CLS
พนักงาน	NN	O	I_CLS
สอบสวน	VV	O	E_CLS

ศาล	NN	O	B_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
ให้	CC	O	I_CLS
ประกัน	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
"	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เอ็นบีที	NN	B_ORG	E_CLS

ต่อมา	CC	O	B_CLS
เวลา	NN	B_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
20.30	NU	I_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
น.	CL	E_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ศาล	NN	O	I_CLS
มี	VV	O	I_CLS
คำสั่ง	NN	O	E_CLS
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
พิเคราะห์	VV	O	I_CLS
แล้ว	AX	O	I_CLS
เห็น	VV	O	I_CLS
ว่า	CC	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	B_CLS
ทั้ง	AJ	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ร่วม	VV	O	I_CLS
กัน	PR	O	I_CLS
ก่อ	VV	O	I_CLS
ความ	FX	O	I_CLS
วุ่นวาย	VV	O	I_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
บ้านเมือง	NN	O	E_CLS
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
บุกรุก	VV	O	I_CLS
เข้า	AV	O	I_CLS
ไป	VV	O	I_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
สถานี	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
วิทยุ	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
โทรทัศน์	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
แห่ง	PS	I_ORG	I_CLS
ประเทศ	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
ไทย	NN	E_ORG	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
ใช้	VV	O	I_CLS
กำลัง	NN	O	I_CLS
ประทุษร้าย	VV	O	E_CLS
โดย	CC	O	B_CLS
มี	VV	O	I_CLS
อาวุธ	NN	O	I_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
เวลา	NN	O	I_CLS
กลาง	NN	O	I_CLS
คืน	NN	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
อีก	CC	O	B_CLS
ทั้ง	CC	O	I_CLS
ยัง	AX	O	I_CLS
ข่มขืนใจ	VV	O	I_CLS
เจ้าหน้าที่	NN	O	E_CLS
ให้	CC	O	B_CLS
หยุด	VV	O	I_CLS
ทำงาน	VV	O	I_CLS
ออกอากาศ	VV	O	I_CLS
รายการ	NN	O	I_CLS
โทรทัศน์	NN	O	E_CLS

สำหรับ	PS	O	B_CLS
ผู้ต้องหา	NN	O	I_CLS
ทั้ง	AJ	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
82	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ประกอบ	VV	O	I_CLS
ด้วย	PS	O	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ธเนศร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คำชุม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ชนินทร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อินทร์พรหม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุธรรม	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จันทวงศ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สัญญา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุขเกื้อ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
จำแลง	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คุ้มสังข์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ปัญญาเดช	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เอกภาณุพัตร์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
มนตรี	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แซ่ลิ้ม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สมถวิล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แซ่เอี้ย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วุฒิชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ช่วยบุญชู	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
มนัส	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สีสายหูด	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ยุทธนา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โอชาพงค์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ธนพัฒน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วิไลภรณ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
นิติรัตน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทรัพย์สมบูรณ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
นัสเซอร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ยีหมะ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุรชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุทธิวรานนท์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ชัชวาล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จันชนะพล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สัมพันธ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อ่อนช่วย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สหัส	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทองวิจิตร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
บัญชา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ดีบรรจง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
เฉลิม	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โลกภิบาล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วิชาญ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
หยะอัด	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ทรงวุฒิ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จุลษร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
กิติกร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ขุนศรี	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
เมธี	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อู่ทอง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ธีรพร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ชูเมือง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สมเกียรติ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
รัตนพันธ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
นพดล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เอี่ยมอุดม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ศุภชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สมทอง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
บุญฤทธิ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เชิญทอง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
คฑาวุธ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ชูศรี	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
จีรวัฒน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คงหนู	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พิเชษฐ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ด้วงช่วย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วิเชียร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เขียวเล็ก	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุรินทร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แก้วหัวไทร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ประเสริฐ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ด้วงทิพย์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ดำรงศักดิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จันทพันธ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
จรัส	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วีระพันธ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อำนวย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เพชรเส้ง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
จรัญ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
หนูสังข์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
มานิต	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อรรถรัฐ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สมโชค	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จันทร์แก้ว	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ประสงค์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ตรัยรัตน์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
กฤษดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
มณีพรหม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อัมรินทร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ยี่เฮง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุรเดช	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วราภรณ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สาโรจน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ดุลยคง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ภิชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทองนวล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ปราโมทย์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พุทธขาว	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ประจิตร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
นุ่นหอม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

น.ส.	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สายใจ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
มณีอุปถัมภ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อดิลักษณ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อนุชาติ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
คำรณย์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อู้สกุลวัฒนา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ธัชชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ทองจิตร	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
นพดล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ขาวเรือง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วีระศักดิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บรรจงช่วย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
รอย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บุญนิล	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุนทร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
รักษายศ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ประสิทธิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
มากแก้ว	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
พรชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บรรจงช่วย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
คมชิต	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พุฒคำ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สมพงศ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สารมาศ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ณรงค์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บัวใหญ่	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
เดโช	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
มะลิลา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
กะวี	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ยิ้มละไม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

น.ส.	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วรรณวิมล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แพสุวรรณ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ประดิษฐ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คงช่วย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วุฒธิไกร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สังข์แก้ว	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วิเชษฐ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คงจันทร์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อำไพ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สิริชยานนท์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุริยา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สกุณา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุนทร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุวรรณ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุเทพ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุวรรณ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วิชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อินทร์พรหม	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
วันชัย	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
รักษายศ	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ไพศาล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุขแก้ว	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ธนพล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แก้วเชิด	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุธี	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จันทวงศ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สมเกียรติ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
หนูใหญ่	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

น.ส.	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
อนัญชญา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เพ็ญพลกรัง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
สุรสิทธิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แย้มประชา	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
แก้วกาญ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
แพสุวรรณ์	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

นาย	NN	B_TTL	B_CLS
ศตวรรษ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จอนทอง	NN	E_PER	E_CLS

