คน	NN	O	B_CLS
รัก	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
'	PU	O	I_CLS
เติ้งลี่จวิน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
'	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ห้าม	VV	O	I_CLS
พลาด	VV	O	E_CLS

เติ้ง	NN	B_PER	B_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ลี่จวิน	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จาก	PS	O	I_CLS
ไป	VV	O	I_CLS
เพียง	AV	O	I_CLS
ร่างกาย	NN	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
แต่	CC	O	B_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
ทิ้ง	VV	O	I_CLS
เสียง	NN	O	I_CLS
เพลง	NN	O	E_CLS
อัน	CC	O	B_CLS
ไพเราะ	VV	O	I_CLS
ไว้	AX	O	I_CLS
ให้	AX	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
แฟน	NN	O	I_CLS
เพลง	NN	O	I_CLS
ได้	AX	O	I_CLS
คิด	VV	O	I_CLS
ถึง	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ล่าสุด	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สินทรัพย์	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	I_ORG	I_CLS
ประกันภัย	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ร่วมกับ	PS	O	I_CLS
เรดคาร์เปด	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	I_ORG	I_CLS
บาย	VV	I_ORG	I_CLS
โชว์โนลิมิต	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ร่วม	VV	O	I_CLS
รำลึก	VV	O	I_CLS
ถึง	VV	O	I_CLS
เติ้ง	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ลี่จวิน	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ผุด	VV	O	I_CLS
คอนเสิร์ต	NN	O	E_CLS
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
แฟน	NN	O	I_CLS
ตัว	NN	O	I_CLS
จริง	VV	O	I_CLS
ห้าม	VV	O	I_CLS
พลาด	VV	O	E_CLS

"	PU	O	B_CLS
15	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปี	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เติ้ง	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ลี่จวิน	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
A	XX	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
Special	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
Tribute	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
by	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สินทรัพย์	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	I_ORG	I_CLS
ประกันภัย	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
"	PU	O	E_CLS

คอนเสิร์ต	NN	O	B_CLS
ที่	CC	O	I_CLS
คุณ	PR	O	I_CLS
ต้อง	AX	O	I_CLS
พา	VV	O	I_CLS
แม่	NN	O	I_CLS
มา	AV	O	I_CLS
ดู	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
โดย	CC	O	I_CLS
ศิลปิน	NN	O	I_CLS
คุณภาพ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อาทิ	CC	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รัดเกล้า	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ป๊อด	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โมเดิร์นด๊อก	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ผุสชา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โทณะวณิก	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อั๋น	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
-	PU	O	I_CLS
ภูวนาท	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มัม	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ลาโคนิค	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นภาดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุขกฤต	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นนทิยา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จิวบางป่า	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สุนทรี	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จวบสมัย	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มัดหมี่	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
-	PU	O	I_CLS
พิมดาว	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พานิชสมัย	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
ดาวใจ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ไพจิตร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
30	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
บท	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
เพลง	NN	E_MEA	I_CLS
ถูก	AX	O	I_CLS
ถ่ายทอด	VV	O	I_CLS
ให้	AX	O	I_CLS
ฟัง	VV	O	I_CLS
แน่	PR	O	I_CLS
ๆ	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
23	NU	B_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
พ.ค.	NN	E_DTM	I_CLS
นี้	AJ	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ศูนย์	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	I_ORG	I_CLS
การ	FX	I_ORG	I_CLS
ประชุม	VV	I_ORG	I_CLS
แห่ง	PS	I_ORG	I_CLS
ชาติ	NN	I_ORG	I_CLS
สิริกิติ์	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เพียง	AV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รอบ	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จอง	VV	O	I_CLS
บัตร	NN	O	I_CLS
ที่	CC	O	I_CLS
ไทยทิคเก็ต	NN	B_ORG	I_CLS
เมเจอร์	NN	E_ORG	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ทุก	NU	O	I_CLS
สาขา	CL	O	E_CLS

