ณัฐณิชา	NN	B_PER	B_CLS
โค่น	VV	O	I_CLS
มือ	NN	O	I_CLS
วาง	VV	O	I_CLS
ทะลุ	VV	O	I_CLS
ตัด	VV	O	I_CLS
เชือก	NN	O	I_CLS
หวด	VV	O	I_CLS
ดันลอป	NN	O	E_CLS

ณัฐณิชา	NN	B_PER	B_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สิริจริยาพร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นัก	FX	O	I_CLS
หวด	VV	O	I_CLS
สาว	NN	O	I_CLS
วัย	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
14	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปี	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
โชว์	VV	O	I_CLS
ฟอร์ม	NN	O	I_CLS
สะแด่ว	VV	O	I_CLS
โค่น	VV	O	I_CLS
มือ	NN	O	I_CLS
วาง	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
5	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อาภาพิมพ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ลำดวน	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ขาดลอย	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เซต	CL	O	I_CLS
รวด	VV	O	E_CLS

ลิ่ว	VV	O	B_CLS
ตัด	VV	O	I_CLS
เชือก	NN	O	I_CLS
เจอ	VV	O	I_CLS
ศึก	NN	O	I_CLS
หนัก	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
แพรวพิสุทธิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ชินศักดิ์ชัย	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เต็ง	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ของ	PS	O	I_CLS
รายการ	NN	O	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
อัด	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พรปวีณ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เปรมทอง	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มา	VV	O	I_CLS
แบบ	NN	O	I_CLS
สบาย	VV	O	I_CLS
มือ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2-0	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เซต	CL	O	E_CLS

ประเภท	NN	O	B_CLS
หญิง	NN	O	I_CLS
เดี่ยว	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รุ่น	NN	O	I_CLS
อายุ	NN	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
เกิน	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
14	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปี	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มีการ	FX	O	I_CLS
พลิกล็อก	VV	O	I_CLS
เกิด	VV	O	I_CLS
ขึ้น	AV	O	I_CLS
เมื่อ	PS	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อาภาพิมพ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ลำดวน	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นัก	FX	O	I_CLS
หวด	VV	O	I_CLS
มือ	NN	O	I_CLS
วาง	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
5	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ของ	PS	O	I_CLS
รายการ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พลาดท่า	VV	O	I_CLS
แพ้	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ณัฐณิชา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สิริจริยาพร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มือ	NN	O	I_CLS
ไร้	VV	O	I_CLS
อันดับ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ขาดลอย	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
0-2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เซต	CL	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
0-6	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
3-6	NU	B_MEA	E_CLS

ณัฐณิชา	NN	B_PER	B_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ทะยาน	VV	O	I_CLS
เข้า	AV	O	I_CLS
รอบ	NN	O	I_CLS
รอง	NN	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
เลิศ	VV	O	I_CLS
ไป	AV	O	I_CLS
พบ	VV	O	I_CLS
ศึก	NN	O	I_CLS
หนัก	VV	O	I_CLS
กับ	PS	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มือ	NN	O	I_CLS
วาง	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ของ	PS	O	I_CLS
รายการ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
แพรวพิสุทธิ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ชินศักดิ์ชัย	NN	E_PER	E_CLS
_	PU	O	O
ที่	CC	O	B_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พรปวีณ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เปรมทอง	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
รอบ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
สุดท้าย	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-3	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ซึ่ง	CC	O	I_CLS
รอบ	NN	O	I_CLS
รองฯ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
และ	CC	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รอบ	NN	O	I_CLS
ชิง	VV	O	I_CLS
ฯ	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จะ	AX	O	I_CLS
มี	VV	O	I_CLS
ขึ้น	AV	O	I_CLS
ใน	PS	O	I_CLS
วัน	NN	O	I_CLS
เดียว	NU	O	I_CLS
กัน	PR	O	I_CLS
คือ	VV	O	I_CLS
วันที่	NN	B_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
1	NU	I_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
มิ.ย.	NN	I_DTM	I_CLS
นี้	AJ	E_DTM	I_CLS
ตั้งแต่	PS	O	I_CLS
เวลา	NN	B_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
09.00	NU	I_DTM	I_CLS
_	PU	I_DTM	I_CLS
น.	CL	E_DTM	I_CLS
เป็นต้นไป	AV	O	E_CLS

ส่วน	CC	O	B_CLS
ผล	NN	O	I_CLS
การ	FX	O	I_CLS
แข่งขัน	VV	O	I_CLS
คู่	NN	O	I_CLS
อื่น	NN	O	I_CLS
ๆ	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มี	VV	O	I_CLS
ดัง	AV	O	I_CLS
นี้	AJ	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รอบ	NN	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คน	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
สุดท้าย	NU	O	E_CLS

หญิง	NN	O	B_CLS
เดี่ยว	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รุ่น	NN	O	I_CLS
อายุ	NN	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
เกิน	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
14	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปี	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อนาอีส	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
นูโสม	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ธัญธิดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ซื่อตรง	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2-0	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เซต	CL	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
6-4	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
6-3	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
วริศรา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ประจวบพันธ์ศรี	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ภัทรพร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สาลีรัฐวิภาค	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
2-1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เซต	CL	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
3-6	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
6-3	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
10-3	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	E_CLS

ชาย	NN	O	B_CLS
เดี่ยว	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รุ่น	NN	O	I_CLS
อายุ	NN	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
เกิน	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปี	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ฐานทัพ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุขสำราญ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รัฐนันท์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ศิริทาวรจันทร์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
9-8	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
(	PU	O	I_CLS
5	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
)	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	O	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ณัฐพล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
วราสินธ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ซอนนี่	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
นาธานซอน	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รัชพล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สง่าเพิ่มพูน	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ธรณ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บริสุทธิบัวทิพย์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-0	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นภัส	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ปัญญาวิภาสวง	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ฐานวัฒน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ผู้อยู่สุข	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-5	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	E_CLS

หญิง	NN	O	B_CLS
เดี่ยว	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
รุ่น	NN	O	I_CLS
อายุ	NN	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
เกิน	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปี	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นภสร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ผิวบางรักษ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พัณณิน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โควาพิทักษ์เทศ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ทรรศพร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
นาคหล่อ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ณัฐธิดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ชำนิประเสริฐกุล	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-4	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ฐิกานต์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
พงษ์ประยูร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปภาวรินทร์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ยิ้มละม้าย	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
9-8	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
(	PU	O	I_CLS
5	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
)	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	NN	O	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มนัญชญา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สว่างแก้ว	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
สุวรรณา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โอลด์ส	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	E_CLS

ชาย	NN	O	B_CLS
เดี่ยว	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ภวิชญ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สอนหลักทรัพย์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
คหบดี	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ปิ่นเพ็ชร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-2	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เชาวลิต	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บุญนารอด	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
วรชน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
รักษ์ปวงชน	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
9-7	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
วายุ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
คุณาลังการ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พลภูมิ	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โควาพิทักษ์เทศ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-3	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ศิรวิทย์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ดาวแสงสว่าง	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชาร์ล	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โรเบิร์ต	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
9-8	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
(	PU	O	I_CLS
1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
)	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	O	I_CLS
,	PU	O	E_CLS

หญิง	NN	O	B_CLS
เดี่ยว	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
พิรดา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุวรรณรักษ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อติกานต์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
งามไตรเลิศ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-0	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นภารัชต์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สว่างแก้ว	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อนัญญา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จันทโรบล	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-1	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ณัชชา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
จิตรอักษร	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
จัสมิน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
โอลด์ส	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-3	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปภัสรา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ร้อยทา	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปริยชนก	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
สุขกัณหา	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-6	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	E_CLS

รุ่น	NN	O	B_CLS
อายุ	NN	O	I_CLS
ไม่	NG	O	I_CLS
เกิน	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
12	NU	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ปี	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
หญิง	NN	O	I_CLS
เดี่ยว	NU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
อภิระมน	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
นครภัณฑ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ณฌา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นฤมิตคุณา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-1	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
มานิตา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บุษราคมวศิษฎ์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
นรีรัตน์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
ขวัญงาม	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-1	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
กมลลักษณ์	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
กิตติถนอม	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ใจเพชร	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
อานนทวีศิลป์	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-2	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	I_CLS
,	PU	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ศิริกัญญา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
บูรณะนายก	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชนะ	VV	O	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
ชวิศา	NN	B_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	I_PER	I_CLS
เสรีรัฐ	NN	E_PER	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
8-2	NU	B_NUM	I_CLS
_	PU	O	I_CLS
เกม	CL	B_MEA	E_CLS

